



SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

jQuery

Python

SQL

UX

UI

PHONE +46 70 553 40 14

EMAIL

jenny.c.borglin@gmail.com

ADDRESS

Flaggskeppsgatan 2 211 14 Malmö Sweden

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full Stack Software Development graduate at Code Institute, Ireland (University Credit-Rated Bootcamp) looking for an entry-level position and an opportunity to start my new career!

Experienced and self-motivated former marketing coordinator with 15 years of marketing, copy, communication and design experience, and strong communication skills (English and Swedish), currently changing career into tech.

LANGUAGES

Swedish Cartesian Cartesia

Danish

EDUCATION

Full Stack Software Developer, Code Institute, Dublin, Ireland

February 2021 - December 2021

University Credit-Rated Online Bootcamp.

- Coding Fundamentals (HTML, CSS)
- User-Centric Frontend Development (User Experience Design, Bootstrap etc.)
- Interactive Frontend Development (JavaScript, APIs, jQuery etc.)
- Data-Centric Development (Python, Flask, MySQL, Mongo etc.)
- Full-Stack Frameworks (Django, payment solutions)

Service Manager for future tourism,

Field of specialization: Marketing, Yrkeshögskolan, Malmö

August 2004 - June 2006

Leadership and Organization, Project development and Project management, Service management, Marketing, Business administration, Concept development, 12 weeks of internship etc.

Political Science, Malmö University, Malmö

September 2001 — June 2002

Political Science: Global Politics and Societal Change, one-year master's.

International Migration and Ethnic Relations, Malmö University, Malmö

August 1998 — June 2000

International Migration and Ethnic Relations, two-year master's programme.

Danish, Komvux Kronborg, Malmö

January 2003 — December 2003

Danish basic course step 1 and 2.

Humanistic and social science, Spyken, Lund

August 1993 — June 1996

Humanistic and social science (Humanistisk linje).

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Advertising Traffic Coordinator at ADONnews, Malmö

September 2012 — December 2020

Leading and co-ordinating campaigns from initial stages through to delivery. Copy, graphic design, communication with the advertiser, analyzing campaigns (visitor data and user experience), inputting ideas on how to improve current practices where required. Identifying and developing a strong understanding of client's core objectives and challenges.

Head of Google Ads Team at ScandiAds, Malmö

September 2010 — August 2012

In charge of Google Ads sales team and result-oriented advertising and marketing campaigns designed to meet customer needs. Including budget management and copy.

Copywriter at 3C-Ads A/S, Copenhagen

August 2006 — August 2010

Ad copy Google Ads. Exposing a clients unique selling point, writing high-converting CTA ads.

Mentor/Coach at Arbete och Integrationscenter, Lernia, Malmö

January 2001 — January 2002

Assist in developing job readiness through assistance with job opportunities suggestions, resumes, internship etc. (Event, Hotel and Restaurant industry)

Guest relations and bartender at Multiple employers, Malmö

January 1995 — January 2004

Guest relations, bartender, hostess, head waiter for many years at different hotels, events, nightclubs and restaurants.